We have just moved into a new house and I have been working hard all morning.
I have been trying to get my new room in order.
This has not been easy because I own over a thousand books.
To make matters worse, the room is rather small, so I have temporarily put my books on the floor.
At the moment, they cover every inch of floor space and I actually have to walk on them to get in or out of the room.
A short while ago, my sister helped me to carry one of my old bookcases up the stairs.
She went into my room and got a big surprise when she saw all those books on the floor.
'This is the prettiest carpet I have ever seen,' she said.
She gazed at it for some time then added, 'You don't need bookcases at all.
You can sit here in your spare time and read the carpet!'